Operations at one of Australia's largest gold mines had to be temporarily suspended
on Friday, after a partial wall collapse at one of the mine's dams.
on Friday, after a wall collapse at one of the mine's dams.
The wall collapse at the Cadia mine came just a few days after two earthquakes hit
the The damage to the dam wall was noticed in the late afternoon on Friday, when
earthquake. huge The wall collapse at the Cadia mine came just a few days after two
earthquakes hit the area.
The damage to the dam wall was noticed in the late afternoon on Friday.
The wall collapse at the Cadia mine came just a few days after two earthquakes hit
the area. The damage to the dam wall was noticed in the late afternoon on Friday.
When workers found a section of the northern dam wall had collapsed into the
southern dam. When workers found a section of the northern dam wall had collapsed
into the southern dam.
When workers found a of the northern dam wall had collapsed into the southern dam.
The dams contain waste products of mining and can contain materials which are
harmful to the environment and human health.
The dams are generally constructed using earth fill and are gradually raised over
time. The dams are generally constructed using earth fill and are gradually raised
over time. The dams are generally constructed using earth fill and are gradually
raised over time.
The company was unable to confirm whether the recent earthquakes had contributed to
the dam's The collapse, but said it was conducting a thorough investigation.